<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IT DOG STORY</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="signals_from_mars_title_image">IT DOG STORY MAIN IMAGE</string>
    <string name="start_your_adventure">START</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>

    <string name="page0">%1$s just graduated from IT DOG University with a degree in computer science. Do you want to apply frontend developer?</string>
    <string name="page0_choice1">Yes, i should apply frontend developer.</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">No, i should take a rest first.</string>

    <string name="page1">You choose to take a rest and go play PS4. Do you think you should look for a job now, %1$s ?</string>
    <string name="page1_choice1">Yes, i will go to find a job now.</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">No, i want to play PS4 now!</string>

    <string name="page2">After few years, you still do not have any job and you became very poor. You start to regard you waste so much time on video game.</string>

    <string name="page3">You are going to have an job interview tomorrow. What are you going to do now?</string>
    <string name="page3_choice1">Go UDEMY to study more before the interview.</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">Skip study and go to the interview directly</string>


    <string name="page4">After self-study in udemy online course, you got more and more knowledge now. What are you going to do now?</string>
    <string name="page4_choice1">Study Again</string>
    <string name="page4_choice2">I am ready to have an interview now!</string>




    <string name="page5">(In the interview) %1$s , What is REACT</string>
    <string name="page5_choice1">REACT is a PC GAME</string>
    <string name="page5_choice2">REACT is a PS4 GAME in 2018</string>


    <string name="page6">%1$s ,You did not prepare enough for the interview. You FAIL !</string>

    <string name="page7">(In the interview) %1$s , What are the advantages of using React?</string>
    <string name="page7_choice1">It is easy to know how a component is rendered, you just need to look at the render function.</string>
    <string name="page7_choice2">React is good for 3D render in PC Game Development.</string>


    <string name="page8">%1$s , What are the differences between a class component and functional component?</string>
    <string name="page8_choice1">Class components allows you to use additional features such as local state and lifecycle hooks. Also, to enable your component to have direct access to your store and thus holds state.</string>
    <string name="page8_choice2">Class component is using for Video Component. Functional component is using for debug purpose.</string>



    <string name="page9">%1$s ,You got the offer! Welcome to join our company as a Frontend Developer! (To Be Continued ...)</string>



    <string name="story_image_content_description">Story page image</string>
    <string name="play_again_button_text">PLAY AGAIN</string>

</resources>






